[
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"4 Cities Have Hosted The Modern Day Summer Olympic Games Name Any 2 (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles , London , Paris Or Athens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Silver Fern Is The Emblem Of Which Nations Rugby Union Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Snooker Player Makes A Break Of Eight Points. Which Three Colours Are Potted? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Red, Yellow & Brown"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Statue Of Billy Bremner Stands Outside The Ground Of Which Football Ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leeds United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Yokouna is a grand champion in which sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sumo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According To A Survey Conducted In 2000 Which 2 People Were Voted The Greatest Male & Female Tennis Players Of All Time Respectively?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bjorn Borg Martina Navratlilova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According to Olympic rules, what number of feathers must a badminton bird (shuttlecock) have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fourteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According to rules of both sports, the top of which net is highest from the ground, Tennis or Table Tennis", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Cole"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Alex Hurricane Higgins & Jimmy The Whirlwind White But Whats Ronnie O Sullivans Nickname", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie The Rocket O Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Approximately how many dimples are in a golf ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Between 300 and 500"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"AQOS is now the longest running sports quiz on TV when was it first broadcast? 1969, 1970, 1971,1972", "answer":0, "answers":["1970"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As at August 2004, who is England's all time top goal scorer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Charlton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As We All Know David Beckham Now Plays For US Team LA Galaxy But Who Is The Coach For La Galaxy", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruud Gullit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As who is Cassius Clay now known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mohammed Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At The 1976 Olympics, Only One Competitor Was Excused The Compulsory Sex Test. Who Was That Competitor?", "answer":0, "answers":["Princess Anne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At The Start Of The 2002/03 Season Who was the Premierships Highest Goal Scorer", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Shearer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At what age can a player join the Seniors Golf Tour 45, 50 or 55?", "answer":0, "answers":["50"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At what age did Will Carling first become England skipper?", "answer":0, "answers":["22"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Silverstone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Course Is The Derby Run Each Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Epsom"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Event Has Steve Backley Won Olympic Bronze & Silver Medals", "answer":0, "answers":["Javelin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Grand Prix Circuit Did Aryton Senna Lose His Life?", "answer":0, "answers":["San Marino , Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Ground Do Scotland Play Their Home International Rugby Union Matches", "answer":0, "answers":["Murrayfield"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Motor Racing Circuit Was Ayrton Senna Killed", "answer":0, "answers":["Imola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Scottish Golf Venue Are The Eden Course & The Jubilee Course", "answer":0, "answers":["St Andrews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Did James Bond Play Auric Goldfinger Waging A Gold Bar On The Outcome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sport did Magic Johnson excel?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Might You See A Crucifix", "answer":0, "answers":["Gynmastics (The Rings)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sport was Fred Perry crowned world champion in 1929?", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Was Hungarian Victor Barna World Singles Champion 5 Times", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Are The Grace Gates", "answer":0, "answers":["Lords"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sporting venue are the Grace Gates?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sporting venue can you visit the oldest sports museum n the world?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord's ( MCC Museum )"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Do Competitors Travel Down The Brabham Strait?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brands Hatch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Would You Find Melling Road?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aintree Race Course"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which venue did Steve Redgrave win his first gold?", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Venue Does The Us Open Tennis Tournament Take place", "answer":0, "answers":["Flushing Meadows"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Back in the 1890's which football club used to wear pink shirts? (Still In Premiership)", "answer":0, "answers":["Everton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Atlanta ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Braves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Baltimore ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Orioles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Boston ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Sox"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Chicago ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cubs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Cleveland ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indians"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Florida ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marlins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Houston ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Astros"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Kansas City ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Royals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Milwaukee ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brewers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The New York ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Philadelphia ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Phillies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The St. Louis ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cardinals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Texas ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Toronto _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bluejays"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Boston ___________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Celtics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Denver _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Nuggets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Denver ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nuggets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Los Angeles _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Lakers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The New York __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Knicks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Seattle ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Supersonics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Utah ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jazz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Before Alex Ferguson Who Was Manager Of Manchester United", "answer":0, "answers":["Ron Atkinson (Red Ron)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Between 1950 And 2000 Name Three Tennis Players Born in Germany That Won The Men's Singles Title At Wimbledon? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker , John McEnroe & Michael Stich"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Between 1961 & 1990 a win in Formula One was worth how many points?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"California Dolls Is A Movie That Was Inspired By And Features Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"California Dolls Is An 80's Movie Comedy About Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Can you name 2 British golfers to win the US Masters in the 1990's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nick Faldo & Ian Woosnam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Canadian Ben Johnson Famously Lost His Olympic Title,World Record & Gold Medal By Failing A Drugs Test At The Summer Olympics But Where & When Did This Take Place ' Where (Country) & When (Year) ''", "answer":0, "answers":["1988, Seoul / Korea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Colin Hendry left Blackburn in 1998 to join which Scottish Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Colin McRae joined which rally team in 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Subaru"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Competitive Swimming Has 4 Events Butterfly, Breast Stroke, Back Stroke, & What Other", "answer":0, "answers":["Freestyle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"David Campeze Was the Leading try Scorer for Which country", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Did The Game Of Polo Originate In India, Persia, Or Argentina", "answer":0, "answers":["Persia (Iran)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"During A Hockey Bully Off How Many Times Must Sticks Touch", "answer":0, "answers":["3 Times"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Dwight York & Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink Were Two Foreign Players Who Were First To Score 100 Goals In the English Premiership Who Was The Third?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thierry Henry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"England play their home rugby union matches at which venue?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twickenham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"England Played Football At The Weekend Or Tried To But Only Managed A 0-0, Draw Who Did They Play Against", "answer":0, "answers":["Macedonia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Euro 2008 Gets Underway Later This Year But Can You Tell Me Either Of The Two Host Countries PFE", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria & Switzerland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Field of Dreams is a film about what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Fighting With Gloves Became Standard In 1867 After The Formulation Of Which Set Of Rules", "answer":0, "answers":["The Queensbury Rules"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Baltimore ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Colts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Buffalo _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bills"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Chicago ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bears"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Cincinnati _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bengals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Cleveland ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Browns"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Dallas _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Cowboys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Dallas ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cowboys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Denver _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Denver ____?", "answer":0, "answers":["Broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Miami __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Dolphins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Minnesota _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vikings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The New Orleans __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Saints"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Pittsburgh ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steelers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The San Diego ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chargers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Seattle _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Seahawks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"For Which Formula One Team Did Both Nigel Mansell & Damon Hill Drive", "answer":0, "answers":["Williams"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"For which International side did Shane Warne play Cricket?", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From which club did Manchester United sign Roy Keane?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nottingham Forest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From Which Country Do The Soccer Team Anderlecht Hail", "answer":0, "answers":["Belgium"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From Which Football Club Did Arsenal Sign Thierry Henry?", "answer":0, "answers":["Juventus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From Which Football Club Did Manchester United Sign Roy Keane In 1993?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nottingham Forest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Green Room, Crystal Cathedral & Walking The Dog are all terms from which sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Surfing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Harry Redknapp was manager of which club before West Ham?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bournemouth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"He holds the NHL record for the most goals scored during the regular season.", "answer":0, "answers":["Wayne Gretzky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"He was the NBA, MVP in 1976, 77, and 80.", "answer":0, "answers":["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"He Wears a No.10 Jersey, I Thought It Was His Position But It Turns Out To Be His IQ Who Was George Best Describing", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Gascoigne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Boston ___________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Buffalo _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sabres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Calgary __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Flames"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Calgary _______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flames"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Chicago _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Blackhawks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Detroit ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Wings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Edmonton __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Oilers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Los Angeles ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Kings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Montreal ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Canadians"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Pittsburgh __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Penguins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The St. Louis __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Blues"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Toronto _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Maple Leafs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Toronto ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maple Leafs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Hockey: The Vancouver ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Canucks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How did Catherine McTavish make Wimbledon history in 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["First Female Empire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How High In Feet Is The Net In A Game Of Badminton", "answer":0, "answers":["5ft"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How is British sportsman Francis Thompson more usually known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daley Thompson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How is Edson Arantes Do Nascimento better known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pele"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How is the chess term \"shah mat\" better known ?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Checkmate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Long does a game of field hockey last", "answer":0, "answers":["70 Mins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Long Does A Game Of Field Hockey Last?", "answer":0, "answers":["70 Minutes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Long In Miles Is A Marathon", "answer":0, "answers":["26"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?", "answer":0, "answers":["16"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Balls Are On The Table At The Start Of A Game Of Snooker", "answer":0, "answers":["22 Including Cue Ball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Cards Are You Dealt In A Game Of Gin Rummy", "answer":0, "answers":["10 Cards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many clubs were there in the Premier League in 1997/8", "answer":0, "answers":["20"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Consecutive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Consecutive Wimbledon's Men's Singles Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win?", "answer":0, "answers":["5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Consecutive Wimbledons Men's Singles Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win", "answer":0, "answers":["5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Dice Do You Have In A Backgammon Set", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Dice"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Diciplines Are There In Mens Gymnastics", "answer":0, "answers":["6 (Vault, Rings, Floor, High Bar, Para Bars, Horse)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many dimples does a golf ball have?", "answer":0, "answers":["336"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Dominoes Are There In A Full Set", "answer":0, "answers":["28"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Draughts Are On The Board At The Start Of A Game", "answer":0, "answers":["24 (12 White 12 Black)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Epsom Derbies did Lester Piggott Win?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many feet high is a basketball net", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many feet high is a basketball net?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Furlongs Are There In A Mile?", "answer":0, "answers":["8"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many games must you win to win a normal set in tennis", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many games must you win to win a normal set in tennis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many hoops are used in a game of croquet?", "answer":0, "answers":["6"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many human players are in a polo team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Human Players Are There In A Polo Team", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Hurdles Are Jumped Over In A 110-Metre Men's Hurdles Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Hurdles Are There In The Men's 110metres Hurdles?", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many hurdles in a 400m hurdle race?", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many hurdles must a runner jump over in the 110m men's hurdles race?", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Jumps Are There In The Grand National", "answer":0, "answers":["30 Jumps"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Lanes Does An Olympic Standard Swimming Pool Have", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Minutes Is A Golfer Allowed To Search For A Lost Ball", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many minutes is a major penalty in hockey", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many minutes is a major penalty in hockey?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many minutes is each period of hockey", "answer":0, "answers":["20"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many minutes is each period of hockey?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twenty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Numbers Are There On A Roulette Wheel", "answer":0, "answers":["37 - (0-36)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many Olympic Gold medals did Carl Lewis win?", "answer":0, "answers":["9"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many People Are In Each Of The Crews For The Oxford & Cambridge Boat Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["9 = 8 Rowers & 1 Cox"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many People In A Tug Of War Team", "answer":0, "answers":["8 People"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Pieces Per Player Are There In A Game Of Backgammon", "answer":0, "answers":["15 Pieces"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Pips On A Standard Set Of Dominoes", "answer":0, "answers":["168 Pips"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are In A Basketball Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are There In A Baseball Team", "answer":0, "answers":["9 Players"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are There In A Baseball Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are There In A Netball Team", "answer":0, "answers":["7"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are There In A Volleyball Team", "answer":0, "answers":["6 Players"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Are There In An Ice Hockey Team", "answer":0, "answers":["11 (Check This) n"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players are there on a soccer team", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players are there on a soccer team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players are there on a water polo team", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players are there on a water polo team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players Comprise An Ice Hockey Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Players In A Rugby League Team", "answer":0, "answers":["13 Players"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players make up a field hockey team", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many players make up a field hockey team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many pockets on a standard snooker table?", "answer":0, "answers":["6"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points are awarded for a drop goal in rugby league?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points are awarded for a safety touch in football", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points are awarded for a safety touch in football?", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Points Are Awarded For A Touch Down In American Football?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points are awarded to the winner of a Formula One Grand Prix", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten Points"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points does a player score for a goal in hurling?", "answer":0, "answers":["3 Points"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points is the bullseye worth in outdoor archery?", "answer":0, "answers":["25"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Points Is The Yellow Ball Worth In Snooker", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many points win a game in badminton?", "answer":0, "answers":["15"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many pounds does the Olympic hammer weigh?", "answer":0, "answers":["16"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many referees work a soccer game", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many referees work a soccer game?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many seams are there on a football (American)", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many seams are there on a football? (American)", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many sides does a baseball homeplate have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many sides does a home_plate have", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many sides does a home-plate have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many stitches are on a regulation baseball?", "answer":0, "answers":["108"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Straight Lines Will You Find On An English Football Pitch?", "answer":0, "answers":["17"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Successive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win", "answer":0, "answers":["5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Suits Are There In A Game Of (Mah Jong)", "answer":0, "answers":["3 Suits"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Are A Team Allowed To Touch A Volleyball Before It Crosses The Net?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Did Lester Piggot Win The Derby", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Did Michael Schumaker Win The World Formula One Drivers Championships?", "answer":0, "answers":["7"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Did Nick Faldo Win The Masters Golf Tournament? Is It (3,5,7)", "answer":0, "answers":["3 (1989, 90 , 96)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many times did Ray Reardon win the snooker world championship?", "answer":0, "answers":["6"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many times did Red Rum win the Irish Grand National?", "answer":0, "answers":["None"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How many times did stirling moss win the world championship?", "answer":0, "answers":["Never"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Do Entrants Hurdle The Water Jump In The Steeplechase", "answer":0, "answers":["7 Times"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Times Was Stephen Hendry Crowned World Champion In The 1990's Was It (6,7,8,9)", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Tournaments Constitute A Golf Grand Slam?", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Many Tournaments make up a Grand Slam In Golf", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Much Did NewCastle Pay For Alan Shearer", "answer":0, "answers":["15 Million"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Much Is The Yellow Ball Worth In A Game Of Snooker", "answer":0, "answers":["2"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Old are the horses in the Epsom Derby?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three Years Old"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How old was Boris Becker when he won his first ever Wimbledon singles Championship?", "answer":0, "answers":["17"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Old Was Steve Davis When He Won His First Snooker World Title", "answer":0, "answers":["23"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"How Wide Is The Beam In Womans Gymnastics", "answer":0, "answers":["4 Inches"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Ian Rush said (If I don't drink my milk, I'll only be good enough to play for) which football team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Accrington Stanley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"If A Cricket Umpire Raises His Arms Above His Head How Many Runs Is He Signalling", "answer":0, "answers":["6 Runs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"If All The Race Courses In Britain Were Listed Alphabetically Which Would Come First ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aintree"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"If you bet a Lady Godiva what would be your stake?", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Pound"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"If You Potted Red, Black & Pink In Snooker What Would You Score?", "answer":0, "answers":["15"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Ignoring the Words 'Football'' And 'Club'' Which Is The Only Team In The 2006/2007 Premiership League Whose Name Contains All The Letters From The Phrase 'Red Card''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchester United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1970 What Did Football Referees Get That They Didn't Have Before", "answer":0, "answers":["Red & Yellow Cards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1976 Sue Barker won her only Grand Slam Final. Which one?", "answer":0, "answers":["The French Open"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1977 Which Horse was Guest Of Honour At The Opening Of The Steeplechase Ride At Blackpoll Pleasure Beach?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Rum"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1980 An Official Was Knocked Unconscious Whilst Measuring In The WHHC What Does The Acronym WHHC Stand For", "answer":0, "answers":["World Haggis Hurling Championships"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1981 Sue Brown became the first woman to compete in which annual sporting event", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1984 Which American Equalled Jesse Owens Four Gold Medals?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1985 who became the first unseeded man to win Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1985, Manchester United player Kevin Moran became the first player to do what in an FA Cup final?", "answer":0, "answers":["Get Sent Off"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1986 Which Boxer Became The Youngest Ever World Heavyweight Champion", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Tyson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1992 Kevin Keegan became manager of which football club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Newcastle United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1993 Who Became Youngest Player To Be Crowned UK Snooker Champion?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie O'Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1994 Oliver McCall Defeated Who To Become World Heavyweight Boxing Champion", "answer":0, "answers":["Lennox Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1994 Which West Indian Batsman Scored 501 Not Out In One Innings", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Lara"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1994, Who Collided With Damon Hill, Shattering His Chance Of Winning The World Title, At The Adelaide Grand Prix?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Schumacher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1995 Which Formula One Driver Signed For McLaren But Couldn't Fit In The Car?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nigel Mansell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1995 Who Did Blackburn Rovers Loose To On The Final Day Of The Season Yet Still Managed To Win the Premiership", "answer":0, "answers":["Liverpool"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1996 Who Lit The Olympic Flame In Atlanta Georgia", "answer":0, "answers":["Muhammad Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1998 Which ManUtd Player Became The Worlds Most Expensive Defender", "answer":0, "answers":["Jaap Stam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1998 Who Became The Youngest Footballer To Score A Hat Trick In The English Premiership", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Owen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1998 Who Became The Youngest Footballer To Score A Hat Trick In The English Premiership?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Owen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 1999 who was voted PFA player of the year?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Ginola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 2005 Who Was Named BBC Sport Personality Of The Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andrew Murray"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 2006 At Which Club Did Roy Replace Niall? ( Roy Keane Replaced Niall Quinn)", "answer":0, "answers":["Sunderland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 2006 Who Was Named As The Highest Paid Female In The World Of Sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maria Sharapova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In 2006 Who Was Voted Overseas Sports Personality Of The Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roger Federer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A 1990 Test Match Against India Graham Gooch Scored A Treble Nelson. How Many Runs Did He Score?", "answer":0, "answers":["333"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A Decathlon What Is The First Event", "answer":0, "answers":["100 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A Decathlon What Is The Total Number Of Metres A Competitor Has To Run?", "answer":0, "answers":["2110 (100,110,400,1500)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In a game of netball how many players on a team are allowed To score?", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A Game Of Snooker If You Achieved A Perfect 147 Break, How Many Times Would You Pot The Black Ball In Total", "answer":0, "answers":["16"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A Game Of Tennis What Score Follows 'Deuce''", "answer":0, "answers":["Advantage"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In a maximum snooker break of 147, how many points are scored on the black ball alone", "answer":0, "answers":["112"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In a nine-ball pool set what colour is the number 2 ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blue"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In A Pefect 147 Snooker Break How Many Points Would Have Been Scored By Potting The Black", "answer":0, "answers":["112"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In american football where is the Orange Bowl?", "answer":0, "answers":["Miami"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In April 2003 Who Became The Oldest Man To Be Rated No1 In The World Tennis Association Rankings At The Age Of 33?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andre Agassi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Athletics Track Races What Does The Ringing Of A Bell Signify", "answer":0, "answers":["The Last Lap"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Australian Rules Football How Many Players May A Team Have On The Field At One Time", "answer":0, "answers":["18"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In BaseBall where do the braves come from", "answer":0, "answers":["Atalanta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In baseball, how many outs are there in an inning?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Baseball, What Name Is Given To The Completion Of A Circuit Of Bases On One Hit", "answer":0, "answers":["A Home Run"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In baseball, who won their first world series in 1969?", "answer":0, "answers":["New York Mets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Billiards, How Many Points Are Awarded For Potting The Red", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Bingo , For What Is The Call 2 Fat Ladies", "answer":0, "answers":["88"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Bowling What Is The Term For Knocking Down All Ten Pins With 2 Consecutive Balls", "answer":0, "answers":["A Spare"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Boxing What Is A TKO?", "answer":0, "answers":["Technical Knock Out"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Boxing What Name Is Given To An Illegal Punch To The Back Of The Head", "answer":0, "answers":["A Rabbit Punch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Boxing Who Suffered Defeats To Tim Witherspoon, Mike Tyson & Lennox Lewis", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Bruno"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Darts From What Number Under 100 , Is It Not Possible To Finish With 2 Darts", "answer":0, "answers":["99"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Englands 2002 World Cup Squad Who Was The Heaviest Player?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Seaman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Field Athletics What Is Thrown The Shortest Distance", "answer":0, "answers":["Shot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Football Who Was Liverpool's Captain When They First Won The European Cup Final In 1977", "answer":0, "answers":["Emlyn Hughes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Football Who Was Liverpool's Captain When They Won The European Cup Final In 1977?", "answer":0, "answers":["Emlyn Hughes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Driver Has Been Disqualified"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Formula One what is the race course called in Italy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Monza"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In golf, what bird's name means two under par", "answer":0, "answers":["Eagle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In hockey, what is the equivalent of a rugby scrum?", "answer":0, "answers":["Face-off"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Horse Racing How Many Furlongs Are In A Mile?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Horse Racing What Is A 'Ringer''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Illegally Replacing A Horse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Horse Racing Which Of the 5 Classics Is Run Over The Longest Distance", "answer":0, "answers":["The St Leger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In horse racing, which three race courses stage the five English (Classics)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Doncaster , Epsom & Newmarket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Indoor Athletic Races, Over What Distance Is The Shortest Sprint Race Run", "answer":0, "answers":["60 m"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Judo, What Colour Belt Follows Yellow ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Orange"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Metres How Long Is An Olympic Size Swimming Pool", "answer":0, "answers":["50 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Olympic Competitions, What Is The Height Of A Diving Board", "answer":0, "answers":["10m"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Olympic Weight Lifting What Are The 2 Methods Of Lifting", "answer":0, "answers":["Clean & Jerk , The Snatch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In pro football a \"sudden death\" period lasts how many minutes long?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Fifteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In pro football a \"sudden death\" period lasts how many minutes long\"", "answer":0, "answers":["15"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Professional World Cup Rugby How Many Minutes Does The Game Actually Last", "answer":0, "answers":["80 Mins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Rhythmic Gymnastics, competitors have four pieces of apparatus: rope, hoop & ball, what is the other piece?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Ribbon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In rugby, what is the equivalent of a hockey face-off?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrum"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In showjumping, how many points are incurred for knocking down a fence?", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Snooker How Much Is a (Red Black Red Green Red) Worth", "answer":0, "answers":["13"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In sport, what do the initials PGA stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Professional Golfer's Association"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Squash Each Game Is Played Until A Player Scores How Many Points", "answer":0, "answers":["15"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In ten_pin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of", "answer":0, "answers":["300"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In ten-pin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three hundred"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Tennis What Have You Achieved When You Score A Point Directly From A Serve?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Ace"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the 1983 Wimbledon men's final who did John McEnroe beat 6-2,6-2,6-2?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The 1990's Which Player Played Both For And Against Chelsea In F.A Cup Finals?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark Hughes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The 1998 World Cup Which 3 Teams Were Knocked Out On Penalties (Point For Each)", "answer":0, "answers":["England , Italy , Holland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the Entire English Football League, Which Football Team Has The Shortest Name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bury"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the game of cricket which bird name means scoring no runs", "answer":0, "answers":["Duck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The Game Of Darts How Much Would You Have Scored If You Achieved A 'Tic Tac Toe''", "answer":0, "answers":["Darts (180)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The Schoolboys Card Game Of The Same Name What Cancels Out A Black Jack", "answer":0, "answers":["A Red Jack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The World Of Motor Sports Which Sporting World Champion Was Born in Blackburn On July 1 st 1966?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Fogarty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In The World Of Snooker Disappeared In 1991 & Was Brought Back In 2005", "answer":0, "answers":["Pot Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Ice Skating Rink"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the world of sport what is 62 feet and 10 inches long and 42 inches wide?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten Pin Bowling Alley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In the world of Tennis how did Gunther Parche gain notoriety in 1993?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stabbed Monica Seles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In this team sport each player gets a chance to play every position.", "answer":0, "answers":["Volleyball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Water Polo, Which Player Wears A Red Cap", "answer":0, "answers":["The Goalkeeper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Context Did Thierry Replace Ian Who Had Previously Replaced Cliff", "answer":0, "answers":["Leading Top Scorer for Arsenal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Context Did Thierry Replace Ian Who Had Previously Replaced Cliff?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leading All Time Goal Scorer For Arsenal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Game Might You Get A Cannon", "answer":0, "answers":["Billiards Pool Or Snooker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Make Of Car Did Michael Schumacher Make His Formula One Debut In 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Jordan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Sport Did Nolan Ryan Once Throw A Ball At A Record Speed Of 100.9 Miles Per Hour", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport did the word 'crestfallen' originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cockfighting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport do you find 'coursing'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greyhound racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport is the Heisman trophy awarded", "answer":0, "answers":["American football"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport is the Heisman trophy awarded?", "answer":0, "answers":["American football"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport is the term 'terminal speed' used?", "answer":0, "answers":["Drag Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Sport Might You Need To Perform An Eskimo Roll", "answer":0, "answers":["Canoeing & Kayaking"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Sport Would You (Catch A Crab)", "answer":0, "answers":["Rowing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In what sport would you find a 'Sukahara'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gymnastics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Year did Steve Redgrave Win His First Gold Medal At The Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["1984"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In What Year was (come on you reds) a no.1 single for Man Utd", "answer":0, "answers":["1994"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Athletic Event Was Colin Jackson A Dominant Figure", "answer":0, "answers":["110m Hurdles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Athletics Even Might You Use A Fosbury Flop", "answer":0, "answers":["High Jump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Athletics Event Are Competitors Known As Either 'Spinners Or Shifters''", "answer":0, "answers":["Shot Putt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Blood Sport Are Banderillas Used", "answer":0, "answers":["Bull Fighting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which British Newpaper Did The First Crossword Appear", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sunday Express"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which British Sport Is A Leather Ball Hit By A Gloved Hand", "answer":0, "answers":["Fives"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Card Game Might You Be Dealt A Yardborough", "answer":0, "answers":["Bridge (No Card Over 9)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which City Does The Cycle Race The Tour De France Finish?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which city is the Cotton Bowl played", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which city is the Cotton Bowl played?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which city is the Hockey Hall of Fame located", "answer":0, "answers":["Toronto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which city is the Hockey Hall of Fame located?", "answer":0, "answers":["Toronto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which City Not Country Were The 2000 Summer Olympics Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sydney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which City Were The 2000 Olympic Games Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sydney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which country did the game of ice hockey originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which country is the famous Maracana stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Country Is The Monza Motor Racing Circuit?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which country was netball invented?", "answer":0, "answers":["America"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Country Were The 1992 Olympics Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Country Were The Summer Olympic Games Held In 2008", "answer":0, "answers":["Beijing / China"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which County Is Lord's Cricket Ground", "answer":0, "answers":["Middlesex"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which County Is The Epsom Derby Raced?", "answer":0, "answers":["Surrey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which decade was cricket's first World Cup Final played?", "answer":0, "answers":["1970's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which English City Will You Find Lords Cricket Ground", "answer":0, "answers":["London"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Are Projectiles Thrown At Stakes Called Hobs", "answer":0, "answers":["Quoits"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Do You Twist", "answer":0, "answers":["Pontoon/Blackjack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Might You Castle", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Might You Come Across A (Dummy)", "answer":0, "answers":["Bridge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Might You Get A Royal Flush", "answer":0, "answers":["Poker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Might You Peg Out", "answer":0, "answers":["Cribbage"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Might You Tug On Your Ear", "answer":0, "answers":["Charades"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which game or sport is a \"Zamboni\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which game or sport is a \"Zamboni\" used\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which game would you have a pitchers mound and an outfield?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Game Would You Use A Spider?", "answer":0, "answers":["Snooker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which Gymnastics discipline would a man do the scissors?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pommel Horse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Olympic Games Did Steve Redgrave Win His First Gold Medal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles In 1984"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Pastime Might You Score A Hit", "answer":0, "answers":["Battleships"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Scandanavian Country Is Gambling Illegal", "answer":0, "answers":["Sweden"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Are The Ashes Trophy Set", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Could You Take Long And Short Corners?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Did Britains Nigel Short, Compete For The World Championship in 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Chess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport did Conrad Bartelski compete for Britain?", "answer":0, "answers":["Downhill Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Do Competitors Soop The Ice And Throw Stones At Houses", "answer":0, "answers":["Curling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Do Players Sweep Ice", "answer":0, "answers":["Curling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Do The Participants Wear Sheep Skin Nose Bands", "answer":0, "answers":["Horse Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport does Lee Westwood play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is a \"hole_in_one\" possible\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is a \"hole-in-one\" possible?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the America's Cup awarded", "answer":0, "answers":["Sailboat racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the America's Cup awarded?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sailing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Americas Cup Awarded?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yacht Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Brit (Mucky Maureen) From Barnsley The Current World Champion", "answer":0, "answers":["Mud Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the Canadian Wayne Gretzky an all time great?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Curtis Cup Contested", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the Cy Young Trophy awarded", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the Cy Young Trophy awarded?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the Davis Cup awarded", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the Davis Cup awarded?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Espirito Santo Trophy Contested?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Lance Todd Memorial Trophy Contested", "answer":0, "answers":["Rugby League"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Is The Lonsdale Belt Awarded", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term \"love\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term \"love\" used\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term \"wishbone\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Football"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term \"wishbone\" used\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Football"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term, \"Hang ten\" used?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Surfing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport is the term, \"Hang ten\" used\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Surfing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Come Across A Boston Crab", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Come Across An Albertross", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Encounter A Face Off", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Encounter A Pommel Horse", "answer":0, "answers":["Gymnastics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Play For The Sheffield Shield", "answer":0, "answers":["Australian Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You See A Double Axel", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Skating"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You See A Hiplock Or Flying Mare?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Start From Pole Position", "answer":0, "answers":["Motor Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Might You Win The Curtis Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport must the ball have a diameter of at least 42.67 millimetres and weigh no less than 45.93 grams?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf Ball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Was Desmond Douglas Britain's Leading Competitor", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport With You Find A Piece Of Wooden Apparatus Exactly 17ft Long", "answer":0, "answers":["(Caber Toss)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would The Game Start With A Tip Off?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would Win The Federation Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Womens Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would You Be Awarded The Lonsdale Belt", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport would you compete for the Waterloo Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crown Green Bowls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would You Encounter a Bed Post, A Six Pack, A Blow And A Cherry", "answer":0, "answers":["Ten Pin Bowling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would You Encounter A Bedpost, A Six Pack, A Blow & A Cherry", "answer":0, "answers":["Tenpin Bowling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would You Encounter A Bully Off?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Sport Would You Expect To Find A Short Stop", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport would you find the \"slapshot\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport would you see a Boston Crab or a Full Nelson", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which sport would you use the Eskimo Roll?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canoeing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Surrey Town Is The British National Shooting Centre", "answer":0, "answers":["Bisley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Type Of Card Game Might You Make A Meld", "answer":0, "answers":["Rummy Or Canasta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Weight Category = Did The Boxer Barry McGuigan Become A World Champion", "answer":0, "answers":["Featherweight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Year Did Daley Thompson Win BBC Sports Personality Of The Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["1982"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Year Did Eddie the Eagle Edwards Leap To Stardom At the Winter Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["1988"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which year did Eddie the Eagle Edwards represent England ?", "answer":0, "answers":["1988"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Year Did Synchronised Swimming Make It's Debut At The Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["1984"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Year Did Torville & Dean Win Olympic Gold With Their Bolero Routine?", "answer":0, "answers":["1984"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which year was Ascot built?", "answer":0, "answers":["1711"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In Which Year Was Shergar Kidnapped", "answer":0, "answers":["1983"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"In which year will London host the Olympic Games", "answer":0, "answers":["2012"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Irishman Stephen Roche Won Which Sporting Event In 1987", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tour De France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Is The Oaks Race , A Race For Colts Or Fillies", "answer":0, "answers":["Fillies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Jaques Villeneuve replaced whom as a driver for Williams?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Coultarde"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Jockey Lester Piggot Once Served 3 Years In Prison For What Crime", "answer":0, "answers":["Tax Evasion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Kevin Keegan & Henry Cooper Both Have A Connection , What Is It", "answer":0, "answers":["Brut 33"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Lincoln, East End, Manchester & London Are All Types Of What", "answer":0, "answers":["Dartboards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Liverpool Won Champions League , Who Scored The First 3 Liverpool Goals (PFE)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stephen Gerrard, Vladimar Smicer & Xabi Alonsco"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Loftus Road is the home of which football club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queens Park Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Monza & Silverstone Are Venue's For Which Sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Formula One Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name 1 Country Where Badminton Is The National Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Malaysia & Indonesia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name A Sporting Team Even In Which The Winning Team Only Move Backwards", "answer":0, "answers":["Rowing / Tug O War"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name Both The Start / Finish Points For The University Boat Race", "answer":0, "answers":["Putney & Mortlake"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name One Of The 3 Years In Which The Olympics Were Cancelled", "answer":0, "answers":["1916, 1940, 1944"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The 3 Balls Used In A Game Of Billiards", "answer":0, "answers":["White,Spot,Red"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo", "answer":0, "answers":["Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The 4 Cities Beginning With The Letter A That Have Hosted The Summer Olympics? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Athens , Amsterdam , Antwerp & Atlanta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The 4 Stations In Monopoly", "answer":0, "answers":["Fenchurch Street, Liverpool Street, Kings Cross, Marylebone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name the famous Italian football team who play in Black and White stripped shirts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Juventus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Famous Sportsman Who Lit The Torch At The Opening Of The 1996 Olympic Games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Muhammad Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name the hockey trophy awarded to the player demonstrating the best sportsmanship.", "answer":0, "answers":["The lady byng trophy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Horse That Won The 2007 Grand National", "answer":0, "answers":["Silver Birch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Rugby Union Trophy For Which England & Scotland Compete", "answer":0, "answers":["Calcutta Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Snooker Player Who Is Nicknamed 'The Rocket''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie O'Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name the sport with Valentino Rossi as a leading competitor?", "answer":0, "answers":["Motorcycling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Squash Shot Where The Ball Hits The Side Of The Wall First", "answer":0, "answers":["A Boast"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Youngest And Oldest Members Of England's 2006 FIFA World Cup Squad", "answer":0, "answers":["Theo Walcott & David James"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Name The Youngest Ever World Heavyweight Boxing Champion", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Tyson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"NICE TEAM THUNDERS Is An Anagram Of Which Football Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchester United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Nordic And Alpine Are Two Main Categories Of Which Sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Of What Was Pluto Platter The Original Name", "answer":0, "answers":["The Frisbee"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On A Netball Players Bib What Do The Letters G.A. Stand For?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goal Attack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On A Yacht, What Are Sheets", "answer":0, "answers":["Ropes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On Tv's A Question Of Sport Who has replaced John Parrot as one of the team captains?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frankie Dettorie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On Tv's A Question Of Sport Who was the other Capt with Ian Botham?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Beaumont"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On Tv's A Question Of Sport Who were the first two team Captains?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry Cooper Cliff Morgan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On What Sport Was john Arlott A Noted Commentator", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On what type of surface are the tennis matches at Wimbledon played", "answer":0, "answers":["Grass"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On what type of surface are the tennis matches at Wimbledon played?", "answer":0, "answers":["Grass"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On What Would You See A Person Perform A Cocked Hat Double", "answer":0, "answers":["Snooker Table"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On which cricket ground was the first test match in England played?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Oval"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On Which Day Of The Week Was The 1997 Grand National Contested?", "answer":0, "answers":["Monday (Due To Bomb Scare)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"On Which Race Course Is The Scottish Grand National Run", "answer":0, "answers":["Ayr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Other than Alain Prost, which driver won three Formula One World Championships in the 80's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nelson Piquet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Other than England, which european country took part in the 1996 cricket World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Netherlands"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Other than skiing, which sport takes place on a piste?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fencing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Other Than The Epee & Foil What Other Weapon Is Used In Fencing", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sabre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Outcrop, Big Wall And Crag Are All Forms Of What", "answer":0, "answers":["Rock Climbing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Over How Many Laps Is The Indianapolis 500 Contested", "answer":0, "answers":["200"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Over What Distance Does Drag Racing Occur", "answer":0, "answers":["1/4 Mile"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", "answer":0, "answers":["3,000 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Over what distance is the Melbourne Cup horse race ran (in metres)?", "answer":0, "answers":["3200"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Over Which Distance Did Steve Ovett Win Olympic Gold?", "answer":0, "answers":["800 Meters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Packy East Had 3 Boxing Bouts All Of Which He Lost When Asked About Them He Said & I Quote ' I Was On The Canvas More Times Than Rembrandt '' How is he better known", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Hope"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Peter Simple, Jack Horner & Ben Nevis have all won which famous sporting event?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Grand National"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Polo consists of 8 periods called what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chukkers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Prior To Joining Manchester Utd In 2007 Which Club Did Cristiano Ronaldo Play For?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sporting Lisbon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Rhona Martin Was Captain Of Which British Olympic Gold Medal Winning Team In 2002?", "answer":0, "answers":["Curling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Ryan gigs's dad was a professional in which sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Rugby League"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Sergei Bubka From The Ukraine Is Often Regarded As The Greatest Ever Athlete In Which Field Event", "answer":0, "answers":["Pole Vault"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Sergey Bubka has set a world record in which field event over 30 times?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pole Vault"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"She was \"Sports Illustrated's\" first female \"Sportsman of the Year\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Billie Jean King"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Shirley Crabtree Was Better Known As Which Larger-Than-Life Character?", "answer":0, "answers":["Big Daddy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Silly Point is a position in which sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Since Steven Mclaren Took Over The Reigns As England Manager As Of The End Of 2006 Who Was The Teams Highest Goal Scorer", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Crouch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Sir Paul Fox created which programme, that is shown on the BBC every year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sports Personality Of The Year"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Snooker player Peter Ebdon has a significant physical disadvantage. What is it?", "answer":0, "answers":["He is colour blind"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"So Far (2008) There Have Been 6 Players To Achieve A 147 Break At The Crucible Ronnie O Sullivan & Ali Carter Both Managed It in 2008 Can You Name The Other Four (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Cliff Thorburn, Jimmy White, Mark Williams, Steven Hendry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Soccer: The New York _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Cosmos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"St Andrews is home to which English Football Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Birmingham City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Steve Davis reached every final of the Snooker World Championship between 1983 and 1989, but who were the two players who beat him (PFE) ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dennis Taylor & Joe Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Steve Davis Reached The Final Of Every World Championship Between 1983 & 1989, Loosing On Just 2 Occasions 1 Point For Each Of The Players Who Beat Him", "answer":0, "answers":["Dennis Taylor, 1985 Joe Johnson, 1986"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Straight, Eight Ball And Nine Ball Are Varieties Of Which Game", "answer":0, "answers":["Pool"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Susan Brown Was the first woman to Take Part In which race", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The 1976 Summer Olympics were held in this city.", "answer":0, "answers":["Montreal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Americas Cup Is In Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Sailing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Colours of the All England Lawn Tennis Club are green and what else", "answer":0, "answers":["Purple"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Duckworth Lewis Method Is Used To Keep The Score In Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The first cricket one-day international was held between england and ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Gallagher Brothers From The Band Oasis Support Which Football Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchester United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Gates To The Entrance Of Wimbledon Are Named After Which Player?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Perry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The German athlete Jurgen Hingsen was always runner-up to which British athlete in major competition?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daley Thompson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The German Athlete Jurgen Hingsen was always runner-up to which British Athlete in major competitions?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daley Thompson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Golden Gloves Championship is in Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Greek God Apollo Accidently Killed His Friend Hyacinthus While Practising For Which Sporting Event", "answer":0, "answers":["The Discus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Green Jacket is presented to the winner of which event?", "answer":0, "answers":["US Masters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Japanese martial art of fencing is called ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Kendo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Latin Phrase 'Citius Altius Fortius'' Is The Motto For Which Sporting Event?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Olympic Games"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Melbourne Cup horse race is held on the first _______ in November.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tuesday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The name of the only weapon in women's fencing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Foil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Nursery End, The Pavilion End & St John's Road Are All Linked With Which Sporting Ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lords"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Pen Hold Grip Is Often Used In Which Sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The person who carries the golfer's clubs is called a(n) ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Caddie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Phrase 'You Cannot Be Serious'' Was Made Famous By Which Former Tennis Star", "answer":0, "answers":["John McEnroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Pittsburgh Steelers Won Which Major Sporting Event In 2006", "answer":0, "answers":["The Superbowl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Pumas Are The Rugby Team Of Which Country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Argentina"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Rockets Basketball Team & The Astros Baseball Team Both Hail From Which US City", "answer":0, "answers":["Houston"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Ski Resort Of Zermatt Stands At The Foot Of Which Swiss Mountain", "answer":0, "answers":["The Matterhorn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Solheim Cup Is The Womans Equivalent Of Whhich Famous Sporting Cup ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Ryder Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Stadium Of Light Is The Home Stadium Of Which English Football Team", "answer":0, "answers":["Sunderland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The Terms Acid, Blunt, Casper & Spine Are All Associated With Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Skate Boarding"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The two tire manufacturers in F1 are Bridgestone and ________?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michelin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The US Tennis Open takes place at which venue?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flushing Meadows"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The very first Olympics were part of a festival to honor which God?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zeus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"The white marks intersecting each five yard line are called ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hash marks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"There Are 2 Major League Baseball Teams In New York City Cab You Name Them PFE", "answer":0, "answers":["Yankees & The Mets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This football team was formerly known as the Frankford Yellow Jackets?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philadelphia Eagles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This is the most coveted trophy in Candian football.", "answer":0, "answers":["Grey cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This sport allows substitutions without a stoppage in play.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This sport is called the \"American pastime\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This team won their first World Series in 1969.", "answer":0, "answers":["New york mets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"This traditional Japanese wrestling sport takes place in a circular ring.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sumo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Tony Drago is a snooker professional from which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Malta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Trent Bridge Cricket Ground Is In Which English City?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nottingham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Two under par on a hole of golf is called a(n) ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Eagle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Until 2001, Southampton Played At The Dell But Have Now Moved To Where?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Mary's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"W A is what position in Netball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wing Attack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"WA is what position in Netball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wing Attack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Was Jimmy Connors left or right handed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Left Handed"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Was The Oxford And Cambridge Boat Race First Contested In The 18th, 19th Or 20th Century", "answer":0, "answers":["19th"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Wembley Stadium Hosted The FA Cup Final On Saturday But How Many Years Did It Take To Build The New Stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["7 Years"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis", "answer":0, "answers":["Let"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Animal is Featured On a Ferrari Badge", "answer":0, "answers":["Horse/Stallion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Annual Sporting Event Takes Place Between Putney And Mortlake?", "answer":0, "answers":["The University Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Are Goldie & Isis", "answer":0, "answers":["Reserve Boats For The Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What are large snow bumps known as in skiing terms", "answer":0, "answers":["Moguls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What are large snow bumps known as in skiing terms?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moguls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Are The 6 Weapons Used In A Game Of Cluedo", "answer":0, "answers":["Candlestick,Lead Pipe, Dagger, Spanner, Rope, Revolver"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Are The Five Colours Of An Archery Target", "answer":0, "answers":["Gold, Red, Blue, Black, White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What are the only two colours a table tennis ball is allowed to be in competitions?", "answer":0, "answers":["White and Yellow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Are The Only Two Fences Not Jumped Twice In The Aintree Grand National? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["The Water Jump & The Chair"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Are The Periods Of Play Called In A Game Of Polo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chukkas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What are the two basic aids in orienteering?", "answer":0, "answers":["Map and compass"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What article of clothing was banned from Ascot in 1971?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hot Pants"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Caused The Cancellation Of The Cheltenham Festival In 2001?", "answer":0, "answers":["Foot & Mouth Disease"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Caps Are Worn By The Australian National Cricket Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Green"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Caps Do The Australian Cricket Team Wear", "answer":0, "answers":["Green"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour flag indicates a fair throw in the shot put?", "answer":0, "answers":["White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Is The 8 Ball In A Game Of Pool", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Is The Right Hand Corner Square On A Chess Board", "answer":0, "answers":["White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Shirts Were England Wearing When They Won The World Cup In 1966", "answer":0, "answers":["Red"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What colour signifies a difficult slope in skiing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Colour Socks Do Chicago's Baseball Team Wear? (Chicago White Socks)", "answer":0, "answers":["White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What comes next in the following sequence (Red, Blue, White, Black, Orange)", "answer":0, "answers":["Black and White (Grey Hounds)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What connects Ray Reardon, Geoff Capes and Christopher Dean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Were All Policeman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Country Does Motor Racing's Jacques Villeneuve Come From?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Country Was The First To Win The World Cup & What Country Was The First To Host It (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Uruguay & Uruguay"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Diameter Is The Circle From Which You A Discus", "answer":0, "answers":["2.5m"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Did Both Arsenal & Chelsea Have In 1928 That No Other Team Had?", "answer":0, "answers":["Numbered Shirts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Did Eddie The Edwards Had To Have 2 Inches Taken Off His What When He Represented England At The 1988 Winter Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["His Chin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What did jockey John White do in 1993 for which he is likely to be best remembered?", "answer":0, "answers":["Won Grand National that was void after false starts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Did The Inter Cities Fairs Cup Change It's Name To", "answer":0, "answers":["UEFA Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Distance Is Covered In One Circuit Of A Modern Outdoor Running Track? ( In Meters)", "answer":0, "answers":["400 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What do runners pass to each other in a relay race", "answer":0, "answers":["Baton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What do runners pass to each other in a relay race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Do The Initials TT Stand For In Connection With The Isle Of Man Motorcycle Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tourist Trophy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Do The Initials TT Stand For In Regard With The Isle Of Man Motorcyle Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tourist Trophy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What do the letters ERA mean in baseball", "answer":0, "answers":["Earned run average"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What do the letters ERA mean in baseball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Earned Run Average"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Do The Letters PB Next To An Athlete's Name Indicate", "answer":0, "answers":["Personal Best"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Do The Opposite Sides Of A Standard Dice Always Total", "answer":0, "answers":["7"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Do You Call A Boxer Who Leads With His Right", "answer":0, "answers":["A South Paw"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Does A Black Flag Signify In Motor Racing", "answer":0, "answers":["Driver Disqualified"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What does it mean if a racehorse is described as a maiden?", "answer":0, "answers":["It hasn`t won a race yet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Does The C Stand For On A Netball Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Centre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Does The Term (Kung Fu) Mean", "answer":0, "answers":["Leisure Time"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What does TKO stand for", "answer":0, "answers":["Technical knock out"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What does TKO stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Technical Knock Out"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Does TT Stand For In Connection With The Isle Of Man Motorcycle Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tourist Trophy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Events Are Involved In A Biathlon", "answer":0, "answers":["Cross Country Skiing & Shooting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What famous race was established in 1903?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tour de France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What football player rushed for 2,003 yards in 1973", "answer":0, "answers":["O j simpson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What football player rushed for 2,003 yards in 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["OJ Simpson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What football team was formerly known as the Frankford Yellow Jackets?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philadelphia Eagles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What game features the largest ball", "answer":0, "answers":["Earthball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What game features the largest ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Earthball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What game might you use a (Flick Serve)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Badminton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What goes to the F.A. cup final every year but never gets used, and never will get used?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Losers Ribbons"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Height Is The Crossbar Of A Goal In Professional Football", "answer":0, "answers":["8 Feet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Horrific Sporting Event Took Place On Saturday The 28 th June 1997", "answer":0, "answers":["Evander Holyfields Ear"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What in 1926, did Gertrude Ederle become the first woman to do?", "answer":0, "answers":["Swim Across The English Channel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What in sport, is 7 feet 9 quarter inches(2.375 metres) in length?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Oche in darts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is 11-12 Inches Long and Can't Weigh Less Than 50 Grams?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Relay Batton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is A Cricket Umpire Signaling When He Raises Both Arms Aloft?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is a GS in netball", "answer":0, "answers":["Goal Shooter"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is a Japanese sumo wrestling tournament called? *a Bisho, a Basho or a Bonko *", "answer":0, "answers":["A Basho"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is A Mashie", "answer":0, "answers":["A Type Of Golf Club"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is A Petanque Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Boules"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is An Oxer", "answer":0, "answers":["A Type Of Jump In Show Jumping"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is Awarded To A British Champion In Boxing", "answer":0, "answers":["A Lonsdale Belt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is Denise Lewis Main Athletic Event", "answer":0, "answers":["Heptathlon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is Ian Botham's middle name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Terrence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is it called when a football team loses possession of the ball due to a misplay", "answer":0, "answers":["Turnover"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is it called when a football team loses possession of the ball due to a misplay?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turnover"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is James Naismith best known for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Inventing Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is Lepidoptery Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Butterfly Collecting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is Linford Christies best time for the 100 Metres", "answer":0, "answers":["9.87"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is soccer star Pele's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Edson Arantes do Nascimento"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the 'perfect score' in a game of Ten Pin Bowling?", "answer":0, "answers":["300"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the average viewing figure for The TV Show (A Question Of Sport) 7, 8, 9, or 10 Million", "answer":0, "answers":["8 Million"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Bed Of A snooker Table Made From", "answer":0, "answers":["Slate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Bed Of A Snooker Table Made From?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the connection between Alex Higgins, Barry McGuigan & Jimmy White?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nicknames Connected With Wind"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Dart Player Eric Bristows Nickname", "answer":0, "answers":["The Crafty Cockney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Down Wind Sail On A Yacht Called", "answer":0, "answers":["The Spinnaker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the emblem on the All Black rugby shirt?", "answer":0, "answers":["Silver Fern"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Fastest Swimming Stroke", "answer":0, "answers":["The Crawl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the final event in a decathlon?", "answer":0, "answers":["1500 metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The First Event In The Heptathalon", "answer":0, "answers":["100 Metres Hurdles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The First Event In Three Day Eventing", "answer":0, "answers":["Dressage"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the formula one course called in Canada ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Montreal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Green Fabric That Covers A Snooker Table Called", "answer":0, "answers":["Baize"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the heaviest class of weight_lifting", "answer":0, "answers":["Super heavyweight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?", "answer":0, "answers":["Super heavyweight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Highest Possible Break In A Game Of Snooker", "answer":0, "answers":["155 Opponent Fouls (Snookered On All Reds) Pot A Colour To Represent A Red Then A Black + 147"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Highest Possible Out Shot In A Game Of Darts", "answer":0, "answers":["170 (t20 t20 Bull)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the international governing board of football (soccer)?", "answer":0, "answers":["FIFA"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the last event in a decathlon ?", "answer":0, "answers":["1500 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Last Event In A Decathlon?", "answer":0, "answers":["The 1500 Metres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Longest Athletics Race In The Olympic Games?", "answer":0, "answers":["50 Km Walking Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the maximum number of clubs a golfer may use in a round?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fourteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Maximum Number Of Clubs Allowed In A Golf Bag?", "answer":0, "answers":["14"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Maximum Number Of Horses Allowed To Run In The Grand National?", "answer":0, "answers":["40"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Maximum Score Possible In A Game Of Ten Pin Bowling", "answer":0, "answers":["300 Points"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the misshapen ear that boxers often have called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cauliflower ear"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Most Landed On Square In A Game Of Monopoly", "answer":0, "answers":["Jail"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Most Popular Finishing Double In Professional Darts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Double 16"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Most Valuble Property In A Game Of Monopoly", "answer":0, "answers":["Mayfair"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the name given to a rower who competes in an individual event?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sculler"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the name of a golf stroke that is 2 under Parr for the hole?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eagle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of Blackpool Football Club's Home Ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bloomfield Road"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of Chicago's American Football Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bears"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The (War Dance) The All Blacks Perform Before A Match", "answer":0, "answers":["The Haka"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The Controlling Body In Flat Racing", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jockey Club"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The Golf Stroke That Is 2 Under Parr For The Hole", "answer":0, "answers":["An Eagle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the name of the Manchester City's old home ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maine Road"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the name of the oldest National Hockey League team in the US?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boston Bruins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The Place Where Ice Hockey Players Are Sent For Breaking The Rules", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sin Bin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate", "answer":0, "answers":["The Catcher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Name Of The White Ball In A Game Of Bowls", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Official Circumference Of A Football", "answer":0, "answers":["27-28 Inches"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the only English football team without a vowel in the first five letters of it`s name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crystal Palace"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Only Sport In Which You Can See Teams Defending Goals Of Different Sizes", "answer":0, "answers":["Water Polo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Only Sport Where The Defending Team Are Always In Possession Of The Ball & The Attacking Team Can Score Without Even Touching It", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the only Swimming Stroke not Started by a dive?", "answer":0, "answers":["BackStroke"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the period of play in a game of polo called", "answer":0, "answers":["A Chukka"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Pitch Called In American Football", "answer":0, "answers":["The Grid Iron"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Proper Oriental Name For The White Suits Often Used In Karate And Judo", "answer":0, "answers":["GI (Geeeeee)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the regulation height for a pin in tenpin bowling? (in inches)", "answer":0, "answers":["Fifteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the score of a forfeited baseball game?", "answer":0, "answers":["36770"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the score of a forfeited softball game?", "answer":0, "answers":["36708"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Sign Language Used By Bookies Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Tic Tac"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Technique Called In Which You Right A Capsized Canoe", "answer":0, "answers":["Eskimo Roll"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Value Of (K) In Scrabble", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Points"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Value Of The Letter (Q) In Scrabble", "answer":0, "answers":["10 points"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The Weight Of A Cricket Ball In Ounces", "answer":0, "answers":["5.5 - 5.75 Ounces"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is the white ball called in bowls?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is The White Ball In Bowls Called", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What is Tiger Woods real first name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eldrick Woods"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Is Tthe Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called", "answer":0, "answers":["The Oche"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Major Sporting Milestone Occurred On 6 th May 1954", "answer":0, "answers":["First Sub 4 Minute Mile"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Material Is The Puck Made Out Of In A Game Of Ice Hockey", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubber"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Name Is Given To The Electronic Eye Used At Wimbledon Tennis Tournaments", "answer":0, "answers":["Cyclops"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Name Is Given To The Pitch On Which American Football Is Played", "answer":0, "answers":["The Gridiron"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Nationality Is Former Snooker World Champion Cliff Thorburn", "answer":0, "answers":["Canadian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What nationality is Gabriela Sabatini?", "answer":0, "answers":["Argentinian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Nationality Is Tennis Player Gabriela Sabatini?", "answer":0, "answers":["Argentine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Nationality Is Tennis Player Michael Chang?", "answer":0, "answers":["American"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What nationality was formula one driver Ayrton Senna?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazilian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Nationality Was The Formula 1 Driver Ayrton Senna Who Was Tragically Killed In 1994", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazilian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What number is by the side of the number 16 on a dart board? (either Side)", "answer":0, "answers":["8 or 7"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Number Is Often Called As (Clickety Click) In Bingo", "answer":0, "answers":["66"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Number Lies Between 15 & 6 On A Dartboard", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What number wood is a driver in golf", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What number wood is a driver in golf?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Numbers Are Either Side Of 20 On A Dartboard", "answer":0, "answers":["5 And 1"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Occurs On The Glorious Twelth", "answer":0, "answers":["Start Of The Grouse Shooting Season"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Olympic Sport Prohibits The Wearing Of A Beard?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What piece of sporting equipment has a maximum length of 42 inches and a maximum thickness of 1 & 1/2 inches?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baseball Bat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Piece Of Sporting Equipment Is 5 Meters Long And 10 Centimetres Wide?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gymnastics Beam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Race Takes Place On An Annual Basis Between Putney And Mortlake?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxford & Cambridge Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Score In Darts Is Known As The Madhouse", "answer":0, "answers":["Double One"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Are Torvill & Dean Famous For", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Skating / Ice Dance"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport did James Naismith invent ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do neither participents or spectators know the score until the end?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Behind & Banana Kick\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Australian Football League"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Hotdog & Bottom Trun\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Surfing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Jerk & Snatch\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Weightlifting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Pist & Telemark\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Pull & Lolly\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Sweeper & Advantage Rule\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Soccer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Tight End & Wide Receiver\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Football (Gridiron)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Toucher & Dead Length\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lawn or Indoor Bowls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Touches & Lunges\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fencing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the Harlem Globetrotters play", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport do the Harlem Globetrotters play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Features In The Stella Artois Tournament?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis / Queens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Has 4 Letters And Begins With A 'T''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf!!!!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport has a hooker in a scrum", "answer":0, "answers":["Rugby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport has a hooker in a scrum?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rugby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport has four different color codes for the balls, ranging from yellow for hot conditions to blue for cold", "answer":0, "answers":["Squash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport has sprint, tandem and team pursuit events?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cycling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Is Carried Out at Bisley In Surrey", "answer":0, "answers":["Rifle Shooting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport is played at Wrigley Field in Chicago Illinois -", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Is Played By The Chicago Bulls", "answer":0, "answers":["BasketBall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Is Played By The Minnesota Twins?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport is Played On The Back Of a Ten Pound Note", "answer":0, "answers":["Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport is sometimes called 'rugger'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rugby union"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport was first introduced into the Olympics in 2000?", "answer":0, "answers":["Trampoline"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport was invented in 1973 by a group of drinkers at a pub in West Sussex?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lawnmower Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Sport Would You Expect To See In A Velodrome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cycling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport would you helicopter to the Bugaboos for", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport would you helicopter to the Bugaboos for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What sport/game is Chris Evert associated with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Surname Has Been Shared By Three Formula One Champions Of The 20 th Century?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hill (Damon, Graham & Phil)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What swimming stroke is named after an insect?", "answer":0, "answers":["Butterfly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL play_offs", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL play-offs?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL playoffs?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Type Of Bowler Might Use A Chinaman", "answer":0, "answers":["A Legspin Bowler"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What type Of Creature Is Sonic In The Computer Game", "answer":0, "answers":["A Hedgehog"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Type Of Fruit Is Depicted On Top Of The Men's Singles Trophy At Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Pineapple"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Type Of Race Got It's Name From A Short Dash Between 2 Churches", "answer":0, "answers":["Steeple Chase"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What type of racing has only two cars competing on the track at the same time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Drag Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Type Of Rock Is Used To Make Curling Stones", "answer":0, "answers":["Granite"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What type of testing was first carried out at the Olympics in 1968?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sex Testing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What vehicles are involved in the \"Tour de France\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bicycles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What vehicles are involved in the \"Tour de France\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Bicycles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Was Alex Ferguson's Team Before He Left To Manage Manchester United?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aberdeen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was Baron Pierre De Coubertin's contribution to sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["He founded the Olympic movement in 1892"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was Evonne Goolagong's married name", "answer":0, "answers":["Cawley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was football player Dick Lane's nickname", "answer":0, "answers":["Night train"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was football player Dick Lane's nickname?", "answer":0, "answers":["Night Train"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was Jack Nicklaus' nickname?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golden Bear"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was Mohammed Ali's original name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cassius Clay"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What Was Officially Recognised As A Summer Olympic Sport At The 1992 Barcelona Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Badminton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was the Australian John Landy the second person to achieve?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Sub Four-Minute Mile"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was the first London club that David Seaman played for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queens park rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was unusual about Ted Schraeder's appearance at Wimbledon in the 1949 tournament?", "answer":0, "answers":["He played whilst smoking a pipe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What was won in 1995 by a Spaniard, in 1996 by a Dane, in 1997 by a German, in 1998 by an Italian & in 1999 by an American?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tour De France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What year did Red Rum first win the Grand National", "answer":0, "answers":["1973"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What's the highest possible finishing score in a game of darts", "answer":0, "answers":["167"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What's the nickname of the University of Georgia football team", "answer":0, "answers":["Bulldogs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What's the nickname of the University of Georgia football team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bulldogs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"What's the stick in golf?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Flag"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Whats the main feature of a speedway motorbike?", "answer":0, "answers":["No Brakes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"When Boris Becker Was The First Unseeded Player To Win Wimbledon, Who Did He Beat In The Final?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kevin Curran"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"When Commonwealth Gold Medalist Judy Simpson Was On Gladiators What Was Her Characters Name", "answer":0, "answers":["Night Shade"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"When England Won The Five Nations Grand Slam In 1980, Who Was The Captain?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Beaumont"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"When Kevin Keagan Left Liverpool To Which Club To Move To", "answer":0, "answers":["Hamburg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"When Maradona performed his Hand of God trick which goalkeeper did he beat?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Shilton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where are the U.S. Tennis Open Championships held", "answer":0, "answers":["Flushing meadows, ny"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where are the U.S. Tennis Open Championships held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flushing Meadows, NY"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where is Capitol Hill?", "answer":0, "answers":["Washington DC"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where Is The Irish Grand National Run", "answer":0, "answers":["Fairyhouse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where Might You Come Across A Chicane", "answer":0, "answers":["On A Motor Race Track"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where was footballer John Barnes born?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jamaica"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1896 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Athens, Greece"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1900 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris, France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1908 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["London, England"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1912 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stockholm, Sweden"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1920 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Antwerp, Belgium"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1924 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris, France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1928 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amsterdam, The NetherlandsERROR: Ret: amsterdam, (the netherlands|holland)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1936 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Berlin, Germany"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1948 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["London, England"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1952 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Helsinki, Finland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1956 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Melbourne, Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1960 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rome, Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1964 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tokyo, Japan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1968 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico City, Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1972 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Munich, West Germany"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1980 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moscow, U.S.S.R."], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1988 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Seoul, South Korea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Where were the 1992 Olympics held ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barcelona, Spain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 150:1 outsider won the Embassy World Snooker Championship in 1986?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 1990 Film Was Set Against The NASCAR Racing Circuit", "answer":0, "answers":["Days Of Thunder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 2 steves were record breaking middle distance runners in the 70's 80's", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Cram & Steve Ovett"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 2004 darts champion is known as The Viking because of his appearance?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Fordham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 2004 Darts Champion Is Known As The Viking?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Fordham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which 3 Athletics Events Do Woman Not Participate In", "answer":0, "answers":["Hammer, Pole Vault, Triple Jump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Acid Is Produced In The Muscles During Strenuous Exercise", "answer":0, "answers":["Lactic"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American Football Team Are Known As The Chargers?", "answer":0, "answers":["San Diego Chargers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American Football Team Are Known As The Falcons", "answer":0, "answers":["Atlanta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American Football Team Won This Years SuperBowl (2006)", "answer":0, "answers":["New England Patriots"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American Heavyweight Boxer Nicknamed 'The Atomic Bull'' Gained The WBC World Title In 1994?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver McCall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American Horse Race Is Run At Churchill Downs?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Kentucky Derby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which American was Olympic long jump champion in 1996?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which animal is on top of rugby's Calcutta Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elephant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which annual race is 4 miles and 374 yards long", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which annual sporting event attracts easily the most spectators (i.e. present, not watching television ) of any in the world with around 10 million?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tour De France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Athlete Was Known As The Buckeye Bullet", "answer":0, "answers":["Jesse Owens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Athlete Won Olmpic Gold In Both The 800m & 1500m At The 1990 Games In Athens In 2004", "answer":0, "answers":["Kelly Holmes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Australian cricketer was sent home from the cricket World Cup in February 2003 after failing a drug test?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shane Warne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Austrian Won Four World Downhill Championships In The 1970's", "answer":0, "answers":["Franz Klammer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Avid Everton Fan Won His Only Snooker World Title In 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Parrott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Baseball Team Won A Record 37 World Series In The 20th Century", "answer":0, "answers":["New York Yankees"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Black American Athlete Burst Hitlers Aryan Party Bubble In 1936 By Winning 4 Gold's", "answer":0, "answers":["Jesse Owens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Boxer Had The Nickname Of The Dark Destroyer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nigel Benn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which boxer is known as the Dark Destroyer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nigel Benn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Boxer Sacked His Manager Frank Maloney In 2001?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lennox Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Boxer Used To Enter The Ring To Tina Turner's ' Simply The Best''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Eubank"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Boxer Was Nicknamed 'The Clones Cyclone''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barry McGuigan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Boys Name Is Also The Name Of The Object Ball In Bowls?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Bridge Is Past First In The University Boat Race", "answer":0, "answers":["Hammersmith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Britain Came Last In The 1988 Olympic Ski Jump Finals", "answer":0, "answers":["Eddie (The Eagle) Edwards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which British athlete's autobiography is entitled (A Time To Jump)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jonathan Edwards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which British Boxer Was First To Win 3 Lonsdale Belts Outright?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry Cooper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which british club became the first to have an all seater stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aberdeen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which British Driver Was Formula One World Champion In 1996", "answer":0, "answers":["Damon Hill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which British man ran the fastest mile in the 80's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Cram"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which British soccer club was managed by Christian Gross?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spurs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Brothers Represented England In The 1995 Rugby Union World Cup And Also Appeared With Their Mother In An Advert For Pizza Hut, All We Need Is Their Surname", "answer":0, "answers":["Rory & Tony Underwood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which brothers represented England in the 1995 rugby union World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rory and Tony Underwood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Chess Piece Always Remains On The Same Colour Square", "answer":0, "answers":["Tthe Bishop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which City Is Set To Host The 2008 Summer Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Beijing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which City Was The First Ever To Host The Olympics Twice", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Class Is The Lowest Weight In Professional Boxing", "answer":0, "answers":["Straw Weight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which club did Jose Mourinho leave to become manager of Chelsea in 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Porto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Colour Ball Is Not Placed Back On The Table If It Is Illegally Potted", "answer":0, "answers":["Red"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Colour Ring Surrounds The Gold Center Of An Archery Target", "answer":0, "answers":["Red"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which contender has won most gold's in any one Olympics? Was it Mark Spitz(Swimming), Nadia Comaneci(Gymnastics) or Raymond Ewry (Track & Field)", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark Spitz (Swimming)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which country always leads the opening Olympic procession?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greece"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Does Chelsea Striker Didier Drogba Represent At International Level?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ivory Coast"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Does The Athlete Merlene Ottey Represent", "answer":0, "answers":["Jamaica"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Has Had The Most Wins At The Angling World Championships", "answer":0, "answers":["France"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Hosted The 1994 World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["USA"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Hosted The 2004 Summer Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Greece / Athens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Hosted The Olympic Games In 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greece (Athens)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Is Set To Host The 2010 World Cup Finals", "answer":0, "answers":["South Africa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Produces The Most Successful Rally Drivers", "answer":0, "answers":["Finland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Turned The Five Nations Into Six In Rugby?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which country was judo developed in?", "answer":0, "answers":["Japan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which country was represented by the athlete Don Quarrie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jamaica"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Won The 2007 Woman's World Cup Final", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany (Beat Brazil 2.0)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Won The Most Gold Medals At This Years Olympics (Bonus Pt For How many)", "answer":0, "answers":["China (51)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Country Won The World Cup First Germany Or Brazil", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which country won the World Cup of Soccer in 1982.", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which county cricket team play their home games at Grace Road?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leicestershire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which crew sank in the 1978 boat race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cambridge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which cricket player holds the world record for the highest individual score in first-class cricket?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Lara"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Cricketer Captained England In 23 Test Matches Between 1986 And 1988?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Gatting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Cricketer Is Nicknamed Beefy And Captained England In 1980 & 1981?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Dart's commentator is known for his hyperbole such as (Alexander The Great was 33 when he conquered the known world, Bristow is 27)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sid Waddell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which darts player became the first in his sport to receive an MBE in 1989?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Bristow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Darts World Champion Is Nicknamed The Viking?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Fordham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Darts World Champion Of The 80's Had the First Names Of John Thomas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jocky Wilson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Disaster Re United The 1966 England & German World Cup Teams In A Charity Match", "answer":0, "answers":["The Bradford Fire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which England Rugby Union international was fined 15,000 pounds for bringing the game into disrepute?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lawrence Dallaglio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which English club was formed in 1887 as Ardwick FC?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchester United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which English football team are nicknamed the Tractor Boys?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ipswich"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which English Football Team Has The Longest One Word Name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Middlesbrough"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which English Footballer Was Sent Off In The 1998 World Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["David Beckham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which English Race Course Is Overlooked By Trundle Hill?", "answer":0, "answers":["Good Wood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which European club has won the most european cups in the 90s?", "answer":0, "answers":["AC Milan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which European Football Club Plays Its Home Matches At The Stadio Delle Alpi?", "answer":0, "answers":["Juventus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Ex-Eastenders Actor, Who Is A Massive Arsenal Fan Was the Ghost Writer For David Beckham When He Wrote His Autobiography (Half A Point For Character Name)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Watt ( Lofty)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Famous Athletics World Record Stood Between 1968 & 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Beamans Long Jump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which famous duo won the BBC Sports Personality Of The Year In 1984?", "answer":0, "answers":["Torvill & Dean"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Famous Ship Do The Runners Pass After Completing 10km Of The London Marathon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cutty Sark"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which famous sporting event first held in 1981, was won by Dick Beardsley?", "answer":0, "answers":["London Marathon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Famous Sporting Team First Began In 1926 When They Were Known As The Savoy Big Five?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Harlem Globetrotters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Famous TV show was introduced by the theme tune The Black and White Rag?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pot Black"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which female gymnast won 3 golds and a silver at the 1972 Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Olga Korbut"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which female tearful athlete was BBC Sports Personality of the Year in 1987?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fatima Whitbread"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Female Tennis Star Was Handed A Two Year Ban After Testing Positive For Cocaine At Wimbledon In 2007?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martina Hingis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Film Starring John Candy Told The Story Of The Jamaican Bobsleigh Team", "answer":0, "answers":["Cool Runnings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which first division football team has been promoted to play in the Premiership next season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sunderland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Club Are The Only Team To Go Through A Premiership Season Unbeaten", "answer":0, "answers":["Arsenal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Club Play Their Home Games At The Walkers Stadium", "answer":0, "answers":["Leicester City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Club's Badge Depicts A Golden Lion On A Claret And Blue Background?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aston Villa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Clubs Motto 'Superbia In Proelio'' Translates Into English As Pride In Battle", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchester City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football country plays in red and white checked shirts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Croatia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Manager Was Reprimanded In 2006 after Criticising Female Officials?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Newell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football player has played first team football for Liverpool 658 times and for Wales 67 times?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Rush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Are Known As The Toffees", "answer":0, "answers":["Everton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team are nicknamed the Swans", "answer":0, "answers":["Swansea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team has played at Wembley more times than anyone else?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leyton Orient"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Has Won The European Cup The Most Times", "answer":0, "answers":["Real Madrid (6 Times)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team lost both the 1998 and 1999 FA Cup Finals?", "answer":0, "answers":["Newcastle United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Managed To Loose The 1974,1978 World Cup Finals", "answer":0, "answers":["Holland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Play Their Home Games At Stamford Bridge", "answer":0, "answers":["Chelsea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team plays at Pride Park ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Derby county"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Plays At The Baseball Ground", "answer":0, "answers":["Derby County"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team plays it's home games at The Dell?", "answer":0, "answers":["Southampton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team was nicknamed the \"Orange Crush\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Denver Broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team was nicknamed the \"Orange Crush\"", "answer":0, "answers":["The denver broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Was The First To Install An Artifcial Pitch", "answer":0, "answers":["Queens Park Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Were Originally Nicknamed The Biscuitmen?", "answer":0, "answers":["Reading"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Football Team Won the 2005 FA Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Arsenal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which football team's home ground is Ibrox Stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rangers Football Club"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Footballer Played For The La Aztecs, Fort Lauderdale Strikers & San Jose Earthquakes?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Best"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which footballer was called (Crazy Horse)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Emlyn Hughes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which footballer was England`s first black player?", "answer":0, "answers":["Viv Anderson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which footballer was sentenced to 3 months at Ford Open Prison in 1984 for drink driving and assaulting a police officer?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Best"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Former BBC Sports Presenter Gave Up His Career In Pursuit Of Spiritual & Religious Beliefs & Was Once Called (As Nutty As A Box Of Frogs) By A Talk Show Host", "answer":0, "answers":["David Icke"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which former British world boxing champion has the middle name Livingstone?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Eubank"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Former Heavy Weight Boxing Champion Has An Identical Twin Brother Called George?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry Cooper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which former Olympian lit the Olympic flame at the 1996 Atlanta Games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Muhammad Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Former Sports Person Became MP For Falmouth & Cambourne In 1992", "answer":0, "answers":["Sebastian Coe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Former Tennis Legend Was Charged For A 10 Million Pounds Tax Evasion In 2002", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Former World Boxing Champion Was Jailed In May 2006 For Dangerous Driving?", "answer":0, "answers":["Naseem Hamed"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which formula one team does Juan Pablo Montoya drive for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mclaren"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Game Makes Use Of Hoops", "answer":0, "answers":["Croquet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which German Golfer Won The Us Masters In 1993", "answer":0, "answers":["Benhard Langer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Goal Keeper Was Beaten By Maradona's 'Hand Of God'' Goal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Shilton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Golfer Is Nicknamed El Ninio", "answer":0, "answers":["Sergio Garcia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Golfer Won Over $9 Million Prize Money In 2000", "answer":0, "answers":["Tiger Woods"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Grade Follows A Yellow Belt In Judo", "answer":0, "answers":["Orange"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Grand Prix Racing Team Are Based In Woking, Surrey", "answer":0, "answers":["McClaren"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Grand Slam tennis event is played on a clay surface?", "answer":0, "answers":["French Open"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Heavweight Boxer Is Known As The Real Deal", "answer":0, "answers":["Evander HolyField"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Horse Won The Grand National In 1992, Winning With An Appropriate Name, As It Was Election Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Party Politics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Horse Won The Grand National In 2007?", "answer":0, "answers":["Silver Birch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Increasingly Popular Winter Sport Was Introduced As An Official Event At The 1998 Games", "answer":0, "answers":["Snow Boarding"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Irishman was World Snooker Champion in 1997?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ken Doherty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Is Always The 3 rd Grand Slam Event In The Tennis Calendar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wimbledon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Is Longer A Baseball Bat Or A Tennis Racket?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baseball Bat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Is Older, The New York Or The London Marathon", "answer":0, "answers":["New York"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which is the heaviest, An Ice Hockey Puck or a Baseball?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Ice Hockey Puck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which is the only country to have played in every World Cup since it started in 1930?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Is The Only English Football League Club Beginning Wi The Letter Q", "answer":0, "answers":["Queens Park Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which is the only English football league team that has a name ending with the letter G?", "answer":0, "answers":["Reading"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Is The Only Non English Team To Have Won The FA Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cardiff City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which is the only position in soccer allowed to handle the ball", "answer":0, "answers":["Goalie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which is the only position in soccer allowed to handle the ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goalkeeper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Italian football club did Paul Gascoigne turn out for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lazio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Japanese Martial Art Uses Bamboo Swords?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kendo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Jump Event Did Carl Lewis Specialize In As Well As The Sprint?", "answer":0, "answers":["Long Jump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which league club did Ali McCoist first play for?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Johnstone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Liverpudlian Won The WBC Light Heavyweight Title In 1974", "answer":0, "answers":["John Conteh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which major sporting venue is located in Richmond Upon Thames?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twickenham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Martial Art Made It's Debut At The 2000 Olympic Games", "answer":0, "answers":["Tae Kwon Do"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Middleweight Boxer Is The Subject Of The Film 'Raging Bull''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jake Le Motta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Modern Gymnastics Event Made Its First Appearance At The 2000 Sydney Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Trampolining"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Moroccan Athlete Became The first Man To Run 5000 m In Under 13 Minutes", "answer":0, "answers":["Said Aouita"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which motorcyclist is known as (Foggy)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Foggarty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Nation Did France Beat 3-0 In The Final Of The Football World Cup In 1998", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which NFL team's defensive unit was nicknamed \"The Purple People Eaters\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Minnesota Vikings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which NFL team's defensive unit was nicknamed \"The Purple People Eaters\"", "answer":0, "answers":["The minnesota vikings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Of These Sports Does Not Allow You To Play Left Handed (Polo, Squash, Fencing, Tennis)", "answer":0, "answers":["Polo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Olympic Sport Prohibits The Wearing Of A Beard", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which piece of sporting equipment is a `biased'?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Crown Green Bowl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which piece of sports equipment is a Louisville slugger?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baseball Bat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Player Lost Successive World Snooker Finals From 1990 To 1994?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Player Scored The Most Goals In International Football", "answer":0, "answers":["Pele"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which player was thrown out of Wimbledon in 1995 after he belted a ball in anger and it hit a Ball Girl?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tim Henman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steffi Graff"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which position is usually played by the tallest member on a basketball team", "answer":0, "answers":["Centre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which position is usually played by the tallest member on a basketball team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Centre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Premiership Club Play Their Home Games At The JJB Stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wigan Athletic"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which premiership football team are nicknamed 'The Toffees''", "answer":0, "answers":["Everton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Premiership footballer has the real name of Sulzeer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sol Campbell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which premiership team used to play at the baseball ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Derby County"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Race Over 200 Laps Is Started With The Words, 'Ladies And Gentlemen, Start Your Engines''?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Indianapolis 500"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which racehorse houses the burial site of Red Rum?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aintree"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which record breaker won the first major Marathon she entered in 1996?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liz McColgan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which rugby ground is sometimes referred to as the Cabbage Patch?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twickenham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Rugby League Club Has Won The Challenge Cup More Times Than Any Other", "answer":0, "answers":["Wigan (15)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Scottish Athlete Struck Gold In The 100m At The 1980 Moscow Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Wells"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Scottish Football Club Boasted The First All Seater Football Stadium In Britain ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aberdeen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Scottish Football Club Is Named After An Irish Monk?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Mirren"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Scottish Golfer Was Captain Of Europes 2002 Ryder Cup Team", "answer":0, "answers":["Sam Torrance"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Shooting Season Begins On (The Glorious Twelth)", "answer":0, "answers":["Grouse Shooting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which snooker player ended Stephen Hendry's five-year unbeaten run at The Crucible?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ken Doherty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Snooker Player Is Nicknamed The Rocket?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie O'Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which snooker player was fined 20,000 for assaulting an official in 1996?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie O'Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport allows substitutions without stoppage in play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Combines Rifle Shooting & Cross Country Skiing", "answer":0, "answers":["The Biathlon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Commences With A (Face Off )", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport do the Detroit Red Wings play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Do The Miami Dolphins Play?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Football"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Do You Associate With The Commentator Ted Lowe?", "answer":0, "answers":["Snooker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport do you associate with the Russian woman Maria Sharapova", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Event Combines Riding, Revolver, Shooting, Fencing, Swimming & Running?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pentathlon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Featured In The Olympics Will You Find The Terms 'Bump, Set, Spike & Pancake''", "answer":0, "answers":["Volleyball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport has a movement called a \"telemark\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport has a movement called a \"telemark\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Skiing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Has The Davis Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Has The Most Umpires Per Player", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis (15-1)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Includes Events Called The Halfpipe, The Slopestyle And The Bordercross", "answer":0, "answers":["Snowboardring"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Is Often Termed As (The Sport Of Kings)", "answer":0, "answers":["Horse Racing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport is played by the Minnesota Twins?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Is Played By The Philadelphia Flyers", "answer":0, "answers":["Ice Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Is Played Over 4 Periods Of 15 Minutes Where Only Two Of The Seven Players Can Score?", "answer":0, "answers":["Net Ball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Is Played With The Heaviest Ball", "answer":0, "answers":["(Ten Pin Bowling)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport is Toxophily?", "answer":0, "answers":["Archery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport takes place in a circle 4.55m in diameter?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sumo Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport takes place in a velodrome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cycling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport uses stones and brooms", "answer":0, "answers":["Curling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sport uses stones and brooms?", "answer":0, "answers":["Curling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Uses The Lightest Ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Was Featured In The Movie 'When We Were Kings", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sport Was Inroduced Into The Olympic Games In 1988", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sporting Couple's Autobiography Is Entitled 'Facing The Music''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Torvill & Christopher Dean"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sporting Event Of 1985 Attracted 18.6 Million Viewers In The Early Hours Of The Morning?", "answer":0, "answers":["Embassy World Snooker (Taylor & Davis)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sporting event starts at Putney, finishes at Mortlake and covers a distance of just 4 miles?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boat Race"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sporting Event Was BBC2's First Ever Colour Tranmission In 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Wimbledon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sporting hero from the 70's died in October 1995 at the age of 30?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Rum"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sporting Milestone Occurred At Iffley Road, Oxford In May 1954?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roger Bannister Ran The First 4 Minute Mile"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sports Star Was Known as The Preston Plumber?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Finney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which sportsman is mentioned in the Simon & Garfunkel song Mrs Robinson?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Dimaggio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sportsman's Autobiography Is Called 'My Side''?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Beckham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Sportswear Company Is The Brand With The Three Stripes?", "answer":0, "answers":["Adidas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Steeplechase Did Party Politics Win In Election Year 1992?", "answer":0, "answers":["Grand National"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Striker Scored The 10,000 th Goal in the English Premier league for Tottenham Against Fulham in 2001", "answer":0, "answers":["Les Ferdinand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Super Bike Champion Acquired The Nickname 'The Lion King''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Fogarty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which swimming stroke is named after an insect", "answer":0, "answers":["Butterfly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which swimming stroke is named after an insect?", "answer":0, "answers":["Butterfly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Swimming Stroke Is The First Leg Of The Medley Relay Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Backstroke"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Swimming Stroke Was Introduced Into Competition In 1952", "answer":0, "answers":["Butterfly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Defeated The World Champions Argentina In The Opening Game Of 1990 Football World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cameroon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Has Won The County Cricket Championships The Most Often?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yorkshire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Have Lost the Most Fa Cup Semi finals", "answer":0, "answers":["Leicester City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Joined Formula 1 Racing In 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jordan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Knocked Out Liverpool In This Years Fa Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Burnley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Team Were The England Cricket Team Playing When Michael Atherton Was Involved In The 'Dirt In The Pocket Scandal''?", "answer":0, "answers":["South Africa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which team won the UEFA cup this year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liverpool"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which television comedian once rowed in the Boat Race?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Laurie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Tennis Player Has Announced they Are To Quit The Sport After It Emerged That They Tested Positive For Cocaine At This Years Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martina Hingis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Tennis Player In 2007 Equalled Bjorn Borg's Record Of Five Consecutive Men's Wimbledon Titles?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roger Federer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which tennis player was famous for the 'You cannot be serious'' outburst", "answer":0, "answers":["John McEnroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Tennis Player Won Wimbledon Twice With An 8 Year Gap Between Victories", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy Connors"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which tennis star wore denim shorts during matches?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andre Agassi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which title has been won by the rider who wears the polka dot jersey in the Tour De France?", "answer":0, "answers":["King Of The Mountains"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which two London clubs did Bobby Moore play for?", "answer":0, "answers":["West Ham & Fulham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Two Sports Comprise A Biathlon? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Cross Country Skiing & Rifle Shooting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which tycoon failed to buy Manchester United in 1998?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rupert Murdoch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Type Of Wood Are Cricket Bats Usually Made From", "answer":0, "answers":["Willow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Uk Football Team Are Known As The Owls", "answer":0, "answers":["Sheffield Wednesday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Uk Leasure Activity Has Caused The Most Fatalities", "answer":0, "answers":["Fishing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Was The Only One Of The Four Tennis Grand Slam Tournaments That Pete Sampras Failed To Win In Men's Singles?", "answer":0, "answers":["The French Open"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which was the second club to win the English Premier League?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blackburn Rovers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which weight division in boxing lies between flyweight and featherweight?", "answer":0, "answers":["Batamweight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which West Indian Fast Bowler Died In 1999 Aged Just 41", "answer":0, "answers":["Malcolm Marshall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which woman swimmer won an individual silver medal for Great Britain in the 1980 Moscow Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sharron Davies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Woman Won The Wimbledon Singles Title For The Last Time In 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy Jean King"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Wood Are Cricket Bats Usually Made From?", "answer":0, "answers":["Willow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Wood Are Cricket Stumps Usually Made From?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Wrestler Got His Name From A Tennessee Williams Character", "answer":0, "answers":["Big Daddy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Which Yorkshire football team plays at home at oakwell", "answer":0, "answers":["Barnsley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who 2 Members Of The England Football Team Missed Penalties Against Portugal In Euro 2004? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["David Beckham & Darius Vassell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Accompanied Steve Redgrave In The Last Three Of His Five Olympic Gold Medals Winning Rows, And Went On To Win A Fourth Gold Himself In 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Matthew Pinsent"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who are the only 3 countries to have taken part in all of the summer & winter Olympic Games (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Great Britain , France and Switzerland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Beat Arsenal In This Year To Become The UEFA Champions League Winner?", "answer":0, "answers":["FC Barcelona"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who beat Betty Stove to win the women's singles title at Wimbledon in 1977", "answer":0, "answers":["Virginia Wade"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Beat Mike Tyson In 1990 To Become Undisputed Heavy Weight Boxing Champion Of The World", "answer":0, "answers":["James Buster Douglas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Beat Muhammad Ali In 1978 To Assume His World Heavyweight Title", "answer":0, "answers":["Leon Spinks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Became The BBC Sports Personality Of The Year In 2006?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zara Phillips"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who became the first black manager of a premiership club when he took over in 1996?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruud Hullit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Became The Oldest Boxer To Retain The Heavyweight Title At The Age Of 45", "answer":0, "answers":["George Foreman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Became World Heavyweight Boxing Champion By Beating Ken Norton After Muhammad Ali Retired In 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["Larry Holmes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did 'Tennis World' name rookie of the year in 1974?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martina Navratilova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did Boris Becker Beat to Win his first Wimbledon title", "answer":0, "answers":["Kevin Curren"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did David Gower Overtake As England's Most Prolific Run Scorer In 1992?", "answer":0, "answers":["Geoffrey Boycott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did Forbes Magazine Name As The Highest Earning Sportsman Of 2006?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Schumacher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did Gazza flick the ball over for the Euro 96 goal against Scotland?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colin Hendry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did John McEnroe Play 3 Times In The Wimbledon Mens Final", "answer":0, "answers":["Bjorn Borg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did Lennox Lewis beat to win his first world heavyweight title?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nobody, Riddick Bowe relinquished his title"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did Mike Tyson Defeat to gain his first HeavyWeight Title", "answer":0, "answers":["Trevor BerBick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did Muhammed Ali Fight In 'The Rumble In The Jungle''?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Foreman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did Stephen Hendry replace as World No1 in the 1989-90 Snooker season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Davis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who did Sue Barker replace as host of the BBC quiz show (A Question Of Sport)?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Coleman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Did Tiger Woods Replace As The World's Number One Ranked Golfer In 1998?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greg Norman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who died in 1995 and was the last Brit to win the Wimbledon Mens Singles Title", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Perry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Ended Up Winning The Formula One Drivers Championship In 2007", "answer":0, "answers":["Kimi Raikkonen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who fell behind Roger Maris in 1961 for the homerun record?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mickey Mantle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who had the nickname 'Golden Bear'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Nicklaus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Has A Best Friend who is known to his close pals as Five Bellies", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Gascoigne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who has made more test match appearances for England than any other cricketer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Graham Gooch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Has One The Most Mens Singles Tennis Titles", "answer":0, "answers":["Pete Sampras"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who has played in the most consecutive baseball games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cal Ripken Jr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who holds 3 World Heavyweight boxing belts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lennox Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who holds the NHL record for the most goals scored during a regular season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wayne Gretzky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Holds The Record For The Most Grand Prix Wins", "answer":0, "answers":["Alain Prost"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who hosted the 1999 cricket World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["England"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who In 1968 Made What Is Known As 'The Jump Into The 21 st Century''", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Beamon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who in 2003 aged 33 became the oldest male tennis player to be number one in the ATP's entry rankings?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andre Agassi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Inflicted Amir Khan's First Ever Professional Defeat On The 6th September 2008", "answer":0, "answers":["Breidis Prescott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who is Edson Arantes do Nascimento better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pele"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who is known as (King Kenny)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenny Dalglish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who is known as Pistol Pete?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pete Sampras"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Is Presently The President Of The Football Association?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prince William"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Is The Billionaire Owner Of Formula One", "answer":0, "answers":["Bernie Ecclestone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who is the last British player to win the women's singles title at Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Virginia Wade"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Is The Only English Cricketer To Have Taken All 10 Wickets In 1 Innings At A Test Match", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Laker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Lit The Olympic Torch At The 2000 Sydney Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Cathy Freeman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who lost Wimbledon singles finals to Boris Becker and Pat Cash?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ivan Lendl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who made 11 appearances for Scunthorpe United between 1979 & 1984 but is far better known outside of football?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Made The First 147 Break At The Snooker World Championships", "answer":0, "answers":["Cliff Thorburn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Might Use A Penholder Grip", "answer":0, "answers":["A Table Tennis Player"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Missed The Penalty That Put England Out Of The 1996 European Championships?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gareth Southgate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Moved Up To The No.1 Ranking For Snookers 1998-1999 Season", "answer":0, "answers":["John Higgins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who on the F.A. Cup the most times during the 70's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Arsenal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Played The Part Of Muhammad Ali In The Bio-Pic Of His Life 'The Greatest''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Muhammad Ali!!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Quit As Liverpool's Manager On February 22 nd 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenny Dalglish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Rode Shergar To Victory In The Epsom Derby?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walter Swinburn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who said if i had to choose between staying married & Snooker it would be snooker everytime", "answer":0, "answers":["Ray Reardon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Scored AS Record 11,174 Cricket Test Runs For Australia", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Border"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Scored England's Last Minute Winning Goal Against Belgium In The 1990 Football World Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Platt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Scored Six Of England's Seven Goals At The 1986 World Cup Football Finals?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gary Lineker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Sobbed On The Duchess Of Kent's Shoulder When She Lost Her Wimbledon Final To Steffi Graf?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jana Novotna"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Succeed Joe Fagan As Manager Of Liverpool?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenny Dalglish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who threw their Olympic Gold Medal in a Kentucky River after being refused a meal at a diner because of his colour", "answer":0, "answers":["Casius Clay / Muhamed Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Beaten By Muhamed Ali In The Bout Entitled The Thriller In Manilla", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Frazier"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was Ben Johnson running for when disqualified in Seoul?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Britains Golden Girl In 2004 Winning Both The 800 & 1500 Metres", "answer":0, "answers":["Kelly Holmes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Captain Of England In 1966 When They Won The World Cup", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Moore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was disqualified after failing a drugs test at the 1988 Olympic Games In Seoul", "answer":0, "answers":["Ben Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Disqualified After Winning The Men's 100m At The 1988 Olympic Games", "answer":0, "answers":["Ben Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was first to win the US Masters five times?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Nicklaus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was football manager at Southampton, Rangers and Liverpool in the 1980's & 1990's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Graeme Souness"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was known as the \"Sultan of Swat\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Babe Ruth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was known as the \"Sultan of Swat\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Babe ruth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was Martina Navratilova's usual ladies doubles partner in the 1980's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pam Shriver"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was PFA Young Player Of The Year In 1995 & 1996?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robbie Fowler"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was sent off on Saturday in the match between Arsenal and Bolton?", "answer":0, "answers":["El-Hadji Diouf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Sportswoman Of The Year In 1971", "answer":0, "answers":["Princess Anne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was stabbed on court at Wimbledon by a fan of her chief rival", "answer":0, "answers":["Monica Seles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was supposed to present Jesse Owens his 100 metre Gold Medal at the Berlin Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Adolf Hitler"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was Tennis Player Andre Agassi Married To Between 1997 And 1999", "answer":0, "answers":["Brooke Shields"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ", "answer":0, "answers":["Martina navratilova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martina Navratilova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the 1990 Wimbledon women's singles runner-up?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zina Garrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The Dutchman Who Became Embassy World Darts Champion In 1998?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raymond Barneveld"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first american to win the Formula 1 championship?", "answer":0, "answers":["Phil Hill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Asian Snooker Player To Be Ranked In The World's Top 10?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Wattana"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Athlete To Exceed a Distance Of Eight Metres In The Long Jump In 1935?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jesse Owens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first black athelete to captain Great Britain's men's team?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kris Akabusi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Black Footballer To Captain England", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Ince"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first bowler to take over 300 wickets in test cricket?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Truman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Boxer To Defeat Frank Bruno In A Professional Fight?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Bonecrusher Smith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first boxer to defeat Lennox Lewis in a professional bout?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver McCall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Boxer To Receive A Knighthood", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Henry Cooper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was the First Britain To Hold A World Javelin Record", "answer":0, "answers":["Fatima Whitbread"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First British Athlete To Hold The World Javelin Record?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fatima Whitbread"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Football Player To Score A Hat -Trick In The World Cup finals?", "answer":0, "answers":["Geoff Hurst"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first footballer to be knighted in this country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Stanley Matthews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Footballer To Receive A Knighthood?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Stanley Matthews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first manager from outside the British Isles to win the English FA Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruud Gullit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first NHL player to score 50 goals in one season", "answer":0, "answers":["Maurice richard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first NHL player to score 50 goals in one season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maurice Richard <-- pronounced \"Reeee-shard\""], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Person To Beat Muhammed Ali in a Professional Fight?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Frazier"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Player To Score 100 Goals In The Football Premiership League?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Shearer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first player to score 100 goals in the Premiership?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Shearer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Professional Footballer To Be Knighted", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Stanley Matthews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Professional Footballer To Score 100 Goals In Both Scotland And England?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenny Dalglish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first spin bowler to take over 500 test wickets?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shane Warne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first to win the grand slam of tennis", "answer":0, "answers":["Don budge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first to win the grand slam of tennis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Don Budge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first unseeded man to win Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first unseeded player to win Wimbeldon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the first woman to compete in the World Snooker Champion?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alison Fisher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The First Woman To Run A Mile In Under 5 Minutes", "answer":0, "answers":["Diane Leather"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The Fist Footballer To Receive A Knighthood", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Stanley Matthews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the last Briton to win the men's singles at Wimbledon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Perry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the NBA MVP in 1976, 1977 and 1980?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the NBA's most valuable player in 1976, 1977 and 1980?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The only Australian To Win The Men's Singles At Wimbledon In The 1980's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pat Cash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the only boxer to knock out Mohammed Ali?", "answer":0, "answers":["Larry Holmes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Was The Only Female To Win A BBC Sports Personality Of The Year Award In The 1990's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liz McColgan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was the only woman to win an athletics gold medal for Britain in the 1992 Barcelona Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sally Gunnell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who was voted BBC's Golden Sports Personality for the last 50 Years in 2003?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Redgrave"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Were Man Utd Playing When Eric Cantona Performed His Famous Kung Fu Kick On A Fan", "answer":0, "answers":["Crystal Palace"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Were The First British Football Club To Have Under Soil Heating?", "answer":0, "answers":["Everton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Were The Only 2 Players To Score For England In The 1986 Football World Cup Finals? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Gary Lineker & Peter Beardsley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won 7 gold Medals In Swimming At The 1972 Olympics", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark Spitz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won a boxing gold medal at Sydney in 2000 in the super heavyweight division?", "answer":0, "answers":["Audley Harrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won A Seventh World Snooker Title In 1994?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alison Fisher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won BBC Sports Personality Of The Year In 2006", "answer":0, "answers":["Zara Phillips"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won His Only World Snooker World Championship In 1979?", "answer":0, "answers":["Terry Griffiths"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won Nine Formula One Grand Prix Races In 2000", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Schumacher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won the 1982 soccer world cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won the 2001 FA Cup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liverpool"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The 2007 Masters Snooker Final On Sunday Night?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie O''Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The 2007 US Super Bowl?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indianapolis Colts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The 2008 Lakeside World Darts Championships", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark Webster"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The 800 Metres At The Moscow Olympics (1980)", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Ovett"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won the Bahrain Grand Prix at weekend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fernando Alonso"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The BBC Sports Personality Of The Year Award In 1971", "answer":0, "answers":["Princess Anne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The Embassy World Snooker Championships In 1998", "answer":0, "answers":["John Higgins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The First University Boat Race Between Oxford And Cambridge?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxford"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won the Ladies singles title at Wimbledon in 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maria Sharapova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won the Men's & Woman's Wimbledon Singles Title In 2007? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Roger Federer & Venus Williams"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won the Spanish grand prix at weekend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kimi Raikkonen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The US Open Men's *Tennis * Title in 1990 At The Age Of Just 19?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pete Sampras"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The Womans Final At The Australian Open At The Weekend", "answer":0, "answers":["Maria Sharapova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who Won The Young Persons BBC Sports Personality Of The Year Award In 2006?", "answer":0, "answers":["Theo Walcott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who won three ladies singles titles at Wimbledon in the 1950's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maureen Connolly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who wore a cabbage leaf under his cap?", "answer":0, "answers":["Babe Ruth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who, in 2002, became the first woman in 11 years to win the BBC Sport Personality Of The Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paula Radcliffe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Who's the current womens world darts champion?", "answer":0, "answers":["Trina Gulliver"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Whose nickname is Beefy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Whose record did Brian Lara beat when he scored 400 not out in a test match in April 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Matthew Hayden's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why Did Henry Viii (8 th ) Ban Bowls", "answer":0, "answers":["To Force People To Take Up Archery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why do some English Football Clubs have triangular corner flags rather than square?", "answer":0, "answers":["Won the F.A Cup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why is September 28 th 1996 a famous date in horse racing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frankie Dettori won 7 races in one day at Ascot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why Was Linford Christie Disqualified From the 1996 Atlanta Olypics", "answer":0, "answers":["2 False Starts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why Was Mathew Simmons In The News in 1995?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Cantona Kung Fu Kick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why was Matthew Simmons in the news in 1995?", "answer":0, "answers":["He was kung fu kicked by Eric Cantona"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why was Mike Tyson fined $3 million by the boxing association in 1997?", "answer":0, "answers":["He Bit Off Evander Hollyfields Ear"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Why Was Number Six Valverde Famous In The Year Of 2006?", "answer":0, "answers":["Won The Grand National"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", "answer":0, "answers":["Glass eye"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With what sport is Chris Boardman associated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cycling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With what sport is Gabriela Sabatini associated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With what sport is Jack Nicklaus associated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport do you associate `Flushing Meadows`?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With Which Sport Do You Associate Harvey Smith, Nick Skelton And Rob Hoekstra", "answer":0, "answers":["Show Jumping"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Babe Ruth associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Bjorn Borg associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Bobby Moore associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Soccer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Chirs Evert-Lloyd associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Jack Nicklaus associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Muhammad Ali associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport is Pele associated ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Soccer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With Which Sport Would You Associate A Lonsdale Belt", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With Which Sport Would You Associate Jahangir Khan", "answer":0, "answers":["Squash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport would you have associated Jocky Wilson", "answer":0, "answers":["Darts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"With which sport would you most associate the commentator Ted Lowe?", "answer":0, "answers":["Snooker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Within Which Sport Might You Encounter The Cyclops System", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""}
]